[Hajime Shacho Ending
That's why
And
August 6
The third is food.
I eat so much that I'm low,
I don't think so. I'm such a cute little body.
So, first you go to a sushi restaurant, right?
I did.
I ate 10 plates of sushi.
I ate ramen.
Same meal meal?
The same evening meal.
You eat 10 plates of sushi and ramen,
And then you have dessert to finish the meal, right?
That's right.
After eating the dessert, I was hungry,
So I ate 5 plates of sushi,
I went back.
I ate dessert again,
I drank all my water,
Thanks for the food.
What?
I did.
But I really love to eat,
Once I start eating, I don't know my limits,
Yes, yes, yes.
I eat for the rest of my life.
Eating a big meal,
But it was not so different from your normal diet?
No different from the amount of food I usually eat,
I always eat like that,
That's how much I ate,
You spilled some on your clothes, didn't you?
That's right.
I ate a lot,
You spilled it, didn't you?
Spilled it,
That's what your fans like about you. Hanae's fans.
Yes, I do. That's right.
All your fans know about it.
Yes, they know.
In Kyushu, for example,
You eat ramen,
Kaede-tama, or something like that,
Yes.
How long can you keep it up?
I can't eat the same thing for a long time.
Is that your policy?
That's right.
That's why I only eat ramen with one refill,
I eat gyoza and rice, and that's about it,
That's about the end of it.
I see. Not everyone in Kyushu likes kaedama so much.
I am the same way.
I like to eat a lot of different foods.
Do you drink alcohol when you are 20 years old?
I haven't had a drink at all since I turned 20.
I think it's great that you drink and drink and drink.
I think you are a great Kyushu man.
I prefer cola to alcohol.
You like Coke more than alcohol?
I sometimes meet people who like Coke,
Do you like Coke?
I like Coke.
Coke and ginger ale.
Really? Ginger ale?
I see.
You don't drink Coke before a show, do you?
I don't drink before a show, but after a show, a Coke is a great drink.
How do you keep in shape like this?
As far as I'm concerned, it's the same.
But maybe it's because I move so much during live performances.
That's right.
I don't move.
No, no, no, no, no, no. It's wonderful.
I'd love to see you eat that food someday.
I'm sorry. Is there anything you won't show me?
No. No.
Really? But...
No, I want to show it to you.
Really? Can we do it?
We'll figure it out.
I'll go get some food, too.
All the members of Girl Power will eat.
Jyoshiryoku? Are you sure? You're spreading it to your sisters.
I'm fine.
Tell them I said something outrageous.
VSHIP Takahashi's "Girl Power" is a big-eating contest.
By all means.
I look forward to it.
We'll be planning this as well.
I look forward to working with you.
Yes, I will. Please do.
Yes, it's wonderful!
It's really great.
Oh, thank you.
No, I'm the starlust. I'm the starlust. I have to learn from you.
This program is...
Mr. Yuki
Mr. Norbert
and Keisuke-san.
Thank you very much!